Contact

9101090633 (Mobile) golapyd@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/golaphazarika (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Computer Science
Front-End Development
Project Planning

Languages

Hindi (Professional Working)
English (Full Professional)
Assamese (Full Professional)

Certifications

Redhat Linux Workshop
Programming on Agent &
Networking
Google Analytics for Beginners
BSNL Training

Best Employee Award

Golap Hazarika

Senior Front-end Engineer & SSO Engineer at Vantage Circle Guwahati, Assam, India

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Laravel, Angularjs, Ionic, Yii, html, css. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering (BEng) focused in Computer Engineering from Anna University.

Experience

Vantage Circle - The one-stop Employee Engagement platform
Senior Software Engineer

April 2018 - Present (6 years 2 months)

Guwahati, Assam, India

AngularJs, Yii 1.1, Angular,

Oauth, Single Sign-On (Okta, Azure, PingOne, SecureAuth, VMware,

Onelogin, ADFS, SAML),

Algolia, Graphql, Chrome Extension, SDK, SQL,

HTML5, SCSS, CSS, bootstrap, javascript, GatsbyJS, EventSource

Mywallz

Software Developer

January 2017 - March 2018 (1 year 3 months)

Guwahati Area, India

Technologies i have worked : Laravel, Angularjs, Ionic, css, HTML5, bootstrap, SQL

The Minacs Group
CSR (Customer care)
September 2014 - November 2014 (3 months)
Bangalore

Resolving Flipkart Customer issue across india.

Education

Anna University

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Computer Engineering (2010 - 2014)

kaliabor college

Class 11 to Class 12, Science · (2007 - 2009)

kuwaritol high school

Class 5 to Class 10 · (2001 - 2007)

Sishu Bidthypith Kuwaritol

Lkg to Class 4 · (1994 - 2001)